http://www.treeclimbing.com/privacy-policy

What This Privacy Policy Covers
This policy covers how Tree Climbers International treats personal information that Tree Climbers International collects and receives in connection with its public website as well as its membership website, Tree Climbers International View. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, e-mail address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.
Information Collection and Use
Tree Climbers International collects personal information when you register with Tree Climbers International View, our membership website, and when you visit Tree Climbers International’s public website.
When you register with Tree Climbers International View we ask for information such as your name, e-mail address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Once you register with Tree Climbers International View and sign in to Tree Climbers International View, you are not anonymous to us.
Tree Climbers International automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Tree Climbers International cookie information, and the page you request.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
Tree Climbers International does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:
When we respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; or
When we believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, and situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Tree Climbers International's terms of use, confidentiality pledge and standards or as otherwise required by law.
Cookies: Tree Climbers International may set and access cookies on your computer.
Cookies are files or pieces of information that may be stored in your computer’s hard drive when you visit a website. This file or piece of information allows a user to move quickly and easily around our website and is used to identify returning users. We also use a cookie to track a user’s sessions. We use this information to find out what site features are most popular so we can develop our website and content in light of our analysis of people’s usage.
The use of cookies is an industry standard and done on most websites.
We do not, however, use cookies to retrieve involuntary information about your computer.
Accordingly, if you would prefer, you can set up your browser to refuse cookies or to alert you to their presence and thereby allow you to remove them from your computer.
Confidentiality and Security
We limit access to personal information about you to staff who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide services to you or in order to do their jobs.
We take all reasonable precautions to keep your personal information secure and we have put in place physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.
If you wish to have your account and all associated information removed from our server, please This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it..
Links to Other Websites
The Tree Climbers International public website and our membership website, Tree Climbers International View, contain links to other Websites; however, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites and do not make any representation as to the existence, sufficiency, accuracy or completeness of their websites or privacy policies.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
Due to changes in legislation and best practice or enhancements to functionality and content on Tree Climbers International’s public website, Tree Climbers International may update this privacy policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary e-mail address or by placing a prominent notice on our public website and Tree Climbers International View, and accordingly you should check here from time to time.
Questions and Suggestions
If you have questions or suggestions, please contact us at Tree Climbers International, Attention: Privacy Officer.
Tree Climbers International, Inc.
1284 Merry Lane NEAtlanta, GA30329-3923USA
Email usPhone: 404-377-3150Fax:     404-458-4303
Proud supporter of:
Website by 3by400, a north Georgia web design team using Joomla!
